{
    "subject": "resource/James_Kay_(Kentucky_politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Kentucky_College_of_Law",
    "human_readable": "James Kay was educated at the University of Kentucky College of Law.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866421222686768,
            "question": "What level of education did James Kay obtain at the University of Kentucky College of Law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9611710906028748,
            "question": "Did James Kay attend college in Kentucky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8736699819564819,
            "question": "Was James Kay's education focused on law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8511486053466797,
            "question": "What institution did James Kay attend for law school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.845218300819397,
            "question": "Can you name the college where James Kay studied law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8144989609718323,
            "question": "Which university is home to the College of Law where James Kay studied?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968823909759521,
            "question": "Where did James Kay receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6339931488037109,
            "question": "What type of institution is the University of Kentucky College of Law?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6225451827049255,
            "question": "In what field did James Kay pursue his studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5746241211891174,
            "question": "Is the University of Kentucky known for its legal program?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Kay was educated at the University of Kentucky College of Law.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3558_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field did James Kay pursue his studies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3558_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of institution is the University of Kentucky College of Law?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3558_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did James Kay receive his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3558_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3558_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the text, James L. Kay II earned his JD from the University of Kentucky College of Law."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document for \"91.txt\" contains information about James Kay, stating that he earned his JD from the University of Kentucky College of Law, which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}